Kunal Wankhede

Jalgaon, Maharashtra | 8605905770 | kunalwankhede958@gmail.com | @portfolio | @linkedin | @github

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Versatile developer with a bachelor's in Computer Science, distinguished for collaborative skills and a track record of independently delivering impactful results. Ample experience in full-stack development, delivering well-documented, tested, and operable code. Efficient in collaborating and communicating new ideas and opinions.

AWARDS AND CERTIFICATIONS

Lensathon Snapchat	Apr 2023
Python (Basic) HackerRank	Feb 2023
IBM Machine Learning IBM	Oct 2022
Android Mobile Program Google	Feb 2022

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: Python, C/C++, SQL (Postgres, MongoDB, MySQL), JavaScript, TypeScript, HTML, Java, JSON, CSS, Sass

Frameworks: React.Js, NextJS, VueJS, NodeJS, Flask, Django, ExpressJS, Bootstrap, Tailwind Css

DevOps and API Tools: Git, Docker, Kubernetes, Azure DevOps, Postman

Cloud and Tools: AWS, Google Cloud, Git, Github, NPM, Figma, Adobe XD, Adobe Photoshop, Figma, Netlify, Vercel

Others: Data Modeling, Data Modeling, Database Administration, Design Patterns, Debugging, Analysis

EXPERIENCE

AR Developer (Intern) | *Snapchat*

March 2023 – Present

- Working as an AR Interaction Developer / Designer to build end to end AR experiences for Snapchat Camera lens on Full time contract.
- My expertise in AR technology has been instrumental in driving the continued success and growth of Augmented Reality.
- Using Javascript, Python, R, for building interactive frontend and UI. Using Lens Studio to design layouts and design system.

Ethical Hacker (Intern) | Maharashtra Police

Jan 2022 - Jan 2023

- while worked as a Ethical Hacker in cyber crime investigation cell office, Bandra (E), Mumbai under the Deputy commissioner of Police supervision. During in this internship period, make case reports and help with victim counselling.
- Provided victim counselling and support, offering guidance and assistance to individuals affected by cybercrimes.
- Utilized a diverse set of tools and technologies, including Linux, Python, C/C++, JavaScript, and Sqlmap, to analyze digital evidence, identify vulnerabilities, and develop countermeasures against cyber threats.

Software Developer (Intern) | *SBIT WLL*

Sep 2021 – Feb 2022

- While completing Software Developer internship, gained hands-on experience in software engineering, cloud architecture, project delivery and collaborations with a cross-functional team of professionals
- Worked on various existing and new projects with team support; Fixed UX for components, improved layouts for upcoming features
- Worked extensively with WordPress to maintain and enhance an e-commerce and other website, ensuring smooth operation and optimal performance for online transactions.
- Used tools and technologies during the internship: Figma for design, Git for version control, JavaScript, WordPress, PHP, React, MySQL, Next.js, and XAMPP for development and deployment.

VOLUNTEER / COMMUNITY WORK

Student Ambassador | *Microsoft*

Oct 2022 - Present

- Building a space for learners to get knowledge of real-world engineering, design, and soft-skills through various sessions, hackathons and 1:1 meetups.
- Collaborating with other communities and helping them organize better events, meetups in local cities

EDUCATION

Moolji Jaitha College, Jalgaon

Bachelor of Computer Applications | CGPA: 8.86

October 2021 - June 2024

PROJECTS

Portfolio | React. Js, Three. JS, JavaScript, Node. Js, Json, npm, vercel

Feb 2024

- Single Handedly developed and designed a portfolio website using React. JS, Three. JS, JavaScript with the aim of showcasing recent achievements and the reach of my abilities.
- @Link

Interstellar | TypeScript, JavaScript, Node.Js, Json, npm, vercel

Sep 2023

- Calculates your birthday date and age on various planets in our solar system. It's a fun way to explore the cosmic perspective of time.
- @Link

Crypto Hunter | React.Js, JavaScript, Node.Js, Json, npm, netlify

May 2022

- This app helps its user to watch over all the crypto currency prices, there last 24hr changes, its market cap and much more.
- @Link